{
    "id": "bf1ed7a2e8a74b60bbe3c1e78ec60007",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "R.K Narayan wrote this book. / This book ........................... by R.K Narayan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was written",
                "has been written",
                "is written"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I bought a diamond necklace. / A diamond necklace .......................... by me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is bought",
                "was bought",
                "has been bought"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I know him. / He ............................ to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is known",
                "has known",
                "is being known"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They invited me to their party. / I .............................. to their party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am invited",
                "have been invited",
                "was invited"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I closed the doors and windows. / The doors and windows ......................... by me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have been closed",
                "were being closed",
                "were closed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team expected to win the match. / The match ........................ to be won by our team.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was expecting",
                "was expected",
                "is expected"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Brutus accused Caesar of ambition. / Caesar .................... of ambition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is accused",
                "was accused",
                "has been accused"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He taught me to read Hindi. / I ................................. to read Hindi.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taught",
                "was taught",
                "have been taught"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "One expects better behavior from an educated person. / Better behavior ..................... from an educated person.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expected",
                "is being expected",
                "is expected"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They were watching the film The Titanic. / The film The Titanic ....................... by them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was watched",
                "has been watched",
                "was being watched"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You must endure what you cannot cure. / What ...................... must be endured.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cannot cure",
                "cannot be cured",
                "cannot cured"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}